Fabiano Da Rosa Gomes

Software Developer

I am a professional with over 9 years of experience in the field systems development and integration. I worked in the development of embedded systems, creation of APIs, web frontend and desktop systems. I am currently part of a multidisciplinary team that takes care of integration of clinical analysis equipment with several systems existing in laboratories and hospitals.

Software Developer

enhancements.

Software Developer

internal applications.

Software Developer

Digicon SA, Gravataí, RS

releases(Linux x86 and ARM)

with optimized content.

self employed, Porto Alegre, RS

VFR Sistemas, Porto Alegre, RS

future code releases and patches.

Authored code fixes and enhancements for inclusion in

Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings

and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and

 Delivered and maintained scalable system architecture to support high-availability Internet site with various

Work History

2019-09 -

2018-08 -

2011-11 -

2019-02

2019-08

Current

Contact

Address

Porto Alegre, RS 91720430

Phone

55051995432916

E-mail

gomes.fdr@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ gomes-fdr

WWW

https://gomes-fdr.github.io/

Skills

C specialist

Software

Technical

Analysis

Python specialist

Development

0000

00000

2014-08 -

Associate of Applied Science: Information Technology Faculdade Senac De Tecnologia - Porto Alegre, RS

 Collaborated on all stages of systems development lifecycle, from requirement gathering to production

Modified existing code to replace problematic functions

Education

2017-12

00000

Programming